besttofind.com 2013-05-08

# BestToFind - Policy Agreement

For the purposes of this privacy policy, the terms "we", "us", "our" and "BestToFind" refer to the BestToFind.com website. The terms "You" and "End-User" refer to You as a user of this Site. 

**Register.** When you register to use our Services, we ask you to provide certain information, which may include your email address, home address, birth year, gender, health conditions, credit card number and zip code, as well as a password for your account. Our Advertisers or Partners will never have access to your personal information unless you agree in advance to provide such access. 

**Sign up to receive email newsletters.** When we send newsletters to subscribers we may allow Advertisers or Partners to include messages in those newsletters, or we may send dedicated newsletters on behalf of those Advertisers or Partners, but those Advertisers or Partners will never have access to your personal information, including your email address.. To unsubscribe from newsletters, click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email newsletter. 

**Device Information.** We may collect information about the computer, mobile telephone, Smartphone or other device you use to access the Services to measure the effectiveness of those Services. 

**Cookies.** We use cookies, pixel trackers, server logs, and any Internet technology in order to measure the effectiveness of the Services and any advertising campaigns, as well as to target meaningful content and ads to our users. 

**Analytics.** We may use third parties to provide us information, reports and analysis about the usage and browsing patterns of users of the Services. These reports contain aggregated data only, and do not identify individual users. 

**IP Addresses.** We log Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to our Web sites and mobile applications. 

**Log Files.** We may also automatically log certain usage information about your use of the Services. This information includes a reading history of the pages you view. 

**Refer to Friend.** If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not store this information. 

**Information collected by Third Parties and Your Ad Choices.** Third parties may collect information about you via the Services. In certain cases, we do not have access to, nor control over, these third parties' data collection practices and we do not assume any liability related to their collection or use. In addition to our own systems, we use DoubleClick, DoubleClick Mobile, Google, Google AdMob, and other third-party Ad Servers to serve and display Advertisements. You have options and choices about the collection and use of information by third parties on our Websites. 

**Compliance with Legal Process.** We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Services; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions). 

**Security.** We follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Other Consideration.** In the future, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, we may include your information among the transferred assets. 

**Change to the Privacy Policy.** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.
